Mende Jovanovski Vatasha 24 Bitola, 7000 (+389) 71 277 749

mende.jovanovski@gmail.com



A highly motivated, hard-working, and detail-oriented person with a passion for learning new skills and completing tasks. A person who gained all of his skills through his work experience with a lot of different types of customers. A person who is calmer and happier when the customer is satisfied and is focused on finding a solution in a difficult situation.

Skills

Conflict Resolution; Critical thinking and problem-solving; Ability to multitask; Decision Making; Creativity; Microsoft Office; Teamwork; Fast learning; Computer Skills; Customer service; Ability to work under pressure, Ability to work in a team; Adaptability; Prioritizing; Detail-oriented; Consistent Communication; Communication Skills (Active listening, Communication method, Friendliness, Confidence, Sharing feedback, Empathy, and Responsiveness).

Experience:

May 2021 - PRESENT

Pizza restaurant Kus - Kus, Bitola - Head Waiter

- Coordination of the staff and helping them in difficult situations
- Customer service and respecting customers' orders along with making them satisfied with the staff service, carefully noticing if the customers have any needs, and analyzing every kind of situation in the restaurant if a task has to be done.
- Working with food and appreciating all the needed policies when working with food service
- Welcoming and accommodation the customer, making sure the customer requires all of his needs or queries, making sure the customer is okay and satisfied with his request, finding a solution for a query if there is one, greeting the customer, and getting ready to welcome a new one

<u>September 2018 - May 2021</u>

Coffee bar Bar Carshija, Bitola - Product Manger and Staff Manager

- Organizing events such as Gigs; Humanitarian parties; Book and Music albums publications; Book trade events; Festive parties;
- Organizing and management for the funds and the Daily-earnings, along with transferring salaries to the staff and managing all of the expenses for the bar's monthly needs
- Cooperation with breweries and organizing events promoting beers

- Making sure the coffee bar interior is okay and updating it every few months
- Ordering all the needed drinks along with glasses, cubes, tubes, and all the needed equipment for the job
- Making sure that the staff is satisfied with the work environment
- Hiring and dismissal of the staff

April 2018 - September 2018

Meze bar 102, Bitola - Waiter

- Customer service and respecting customers' orders and making them satisfied with the staff service.
- Preparing for the working day and carefully checking if all the needed drinks are enough, ordering new ones, or making sure to find a drink in the middle of the party if needed.

2015 - April 2018

Carpenter Assistant

- Work under pressure
- A place for creativity and the development of many ideas about the kitchen, dining room, living room, and bedroom furniture look. Meanwhile satisfying the customer and finding the compromise between how something a customer wants to look and how the thing can actually look.

Education

<u>September 2011 - June 2015</u>

Taki Daskalo High school, Bitola -Gymnasium

<u>Languages</u>

English language (reading, writing, speaking, and listening) - Level C1

Macedonian language (native speaker)

Certificates

European Commission Erasmus + Youthpass Mobility of youth workers - Participation in a learning mobility project Digital Europe; (Project hosted by GET INNOVATION BITOLA 01.07.2016 - 10.07.2016 Bitola, Macedonia)

European Commission Erasmus + Youthpass Youth Exchanges - Participation in See the Heart - A youth exchange with 39 young people from the Czech Republic, Estonia, Macedonia, Italy, and Spain.; (Project hosted by 196PAESI Roma 03.09.20016 - 09.09.2016 Cefalu, Italy)

European Commission Erasmus + Youthpass Youth Exchanges - Participation in Safe Drive Saves life; A youth exchange with 40 young people from Poland, Estonia, Macedonia, Romania, and Slovak Republic. (Project hosted by GET INNOVATION BITOLA 15.04.2016 - 24.04.2016 Struga, Macedonia).

Hobbies

Computer Gaming (WOW, Dota chess)

YouTube videos watching (especially about gaming)

Ping pong

Movies and series